[MUFFLED "HYMN TO RED OCTOBER"
PLAYING WITH RUSSIAN LYRICS]
[SINGING GROWS LOUDER]
["HYMN TO RED OCTOBER"
CONTINUES AT FULL VOLUME]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[TRUCK ENGINE RUMBLING]
[HYDRAULICS HISSING]
[SOLDIER SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[SOLDIERS SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[CHAINS RATTLING]
[SOLDIER SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
[WIND HOWLING]
[SOLDIER LAUGHING]
[CHAINS RATTLING]
["HYMN TO RED OCTOBER"
CONTINUES PLAYING]
[MUFFLED CLAMORING
AND BANGING INSIDE]
-[LOUD CLAMORING]
-[BANGING]
[MEN SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN,
WHISTLING]
[SHOUTING AND BANGING CONTINUE]
-[BUZZER BLARES]
-[SONG ENDS]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[CHUCKLES]
No.
["GRUPPA KROVI" PLAYING OVER
SPEAKERS WITH RUSSIAN LYRICS]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER
IN RUSSIAN]
[LAUGHING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[INMATES GRUNT]
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
[INMATES GASPING, CRYING OUT]
[GUARDS SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[CHUCKLES]
Mm. [CHUCKLES]
[DOOR BANGS SHUT]
...Kraven.
Kraven?
-[GRUNTING]
-[INMATE CRIES OUT]
[INMATE WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING]
No.
[GRUNTING VICIOUSLY]
[CHOKING GASPS]
[GRUNTING FIERCELY]
-[GUARD YELLING]
-[GRUNTS]
-[STRAINED GRUNTING]
-[ALARM BLARING]
[GUARD SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
[PANTING]
[GUARD SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[GRUNTING]
[GUARDS SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
[LAUGHING]
[SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
[GUARDS CONTINUE SHOUTING
IN RUSSIAN]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
-[PANTING]
-[DISTANT SHOUTING]
-[WIND HOWLING]
-[LOW GROWLING]
[PANTING]
[WOLVES HOWLING]
-[PANTING]
-[WOLF SNARLING]
[BARKING, SNARLING]
[WHINES SOFTLY]
[WHINES]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
Move! Move! Move!
PILOT: [OVER RADIO]
You were late.
Next time, you break out of
prison and I fly this thing.
No, thanks.
So, how'd it go?
How it always goes.
Good for me...
bad for him.
[HEADPHONES DROP TO FLOOR]
SOLDIER:
Nyet.
[ROARING]
[LOW SNARLING]
[SEAGULLS SCREECHING]
[STUDENTS SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY, LAUGHING]
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
Kravinoff and Kravinoff!
Your father is coming
to pick you up!
What'd you do?
Me?
[CHUCKLES]
Nothing. I thought it was you.
No.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS]
Where are we going, Papa?
We're in the middle of a term
at school.
Sergei...
Mom never made us
do shit like this.
Sergei...
...your mother is dead.
She took own life.
She was weak.
Sick in her mind.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
It was her choice.
Well, she died
because you sent her away.
No.
She gave up long ago.
You haven't even seen her
for two years.
Nothing will change for you.
Or for you, Dmitri.
Where are we going, Papa?
To the funeral?
If you take own life, you do
not get honor of funeral.
So then, where are
you taking us?
We go to hunt.
There have been new sightings
of lion, Zar.
It will be good for you.
Both.
To join men,
be one with nature.
Shoot to kill.
Fun.
[JET ENGINE WHIRRING]
GRANDMOTHER:
Careful with those.
Put the cards away now,
Calypso.
Your mum and dad
will be back soon,
and you know the way
they feel about all this.
It's just a game, Granny.
You think my cards
are just pretty pictures.
Think again, Calypso.
They show us the unseen road.
What?
-Like, predict the future?
-Mm-hmm.
In the right hands.
Lay three cards down.
The first card is the subject.
CALYPSO:
The High Priestess?
You do come from a long line
of very powerful women.
The second card is
the situation.
The Tower.
There's going to be
a terrible accident.
The third card is the outcome.
Strength.
There is great danger
in that card.
I have something
for you, Calypso.
I was going to wait
until you were older,
but the cards have shown us
you will need it very soon.
What is it?
A potion.
The formula has been
passed down
in our family for generations.
What does that symbol mean?
GRANDMOTHER: It's a sign
of the spirit Papa Legba.
He opens the gate
to the other side.
Protect it.
Very powerful.
Go ahead.
It will heal whoever drinks it
in undreamed-of ways.
The time is coming soon.
You'll know what to do with it.
Now, put those away
before your parents get back.
[BIRDS CAWING]
[GUNSHOT ECHOES]
Well done, Nikolai.
[ANTELOPE WHEEZING QUIETLY]
Sergei.
You see? So beautiful.
Never fear death.
They are prey.
We are predators.
Men should be only animal
that is dreaded.
Dmitri, don't look so weak.
Be a man.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
SERGEI:
You all right?
DMITRI:
Yeah.
He shouldn't have talked
to you like that.
Yeah, well...
...he's an asshole.
There's nothing
I can do about that.
He'll never respect me
like he respects you.
Want to bet?
[LAUGHS SOFTLY]
[SERGEI SIGHS]
DMITRI:
I miss Mom.
SERGEI:
Me, too, Dima. Me, too.
[LION ROARING IN DISTANCE]
Is it the Zar?
Not even pussycat.
Perhaps it's the Zar's
illegitimate half-brother.
[CHUCKLING SOFTLY]
Like your Dmitri.
NIKOLAI:
Leave the boy.
He carries no blame
for his father's wandering eye.
You will know Zar
when you hear.
He sound like thunder
from mountaintop.
You have seen this beast?
I have seen his work.
This cat has killed two dozen,
maybe three dozen men.
Yes?
For as long as men like you
have been coming down here
to kill lions,
there have been legends
of the one who can't be killed.
NIKOLAI:
Men like me.
But you still take my money,
don't you, Bahari?
A lion hunts for food.
Same as I do.
Why do you hunt, Nikolai?
You know this, Bahari.
Men who kill legend
becomes legend.
[DISTANT THUNDER RUMBLING]
ALEKSEI: [BREATHLESSLY]
Nikolai...
we should talk.
Save your breath.
No, it's a condition.
I'll be okay, as long as I take
a few breaks here and there.
One thing that you should know
about me is that
I'm always thinking
of the future.
I want you to be my partner.
What is your name?
I'm a guest here of Vladimir.
Aleksei Sytsevich.
No.
You do not have name.
In this world,
you barely exist.
So, what can some
no-name, nonexistent,
condition-suffering fool
offer up to the Kravinoffs?
-Nothing.
-[SHORT CHUCKLE]
I am here...
teaching my sons
the joy of stalking,
and you and your imbecilic
voice are stalking me.
So, be quiet.
Hope Father gets him this time.
Why?
Well, because then
he'll become a legend,
and we don't have
to come here again.
A true legend would fight fair.
Not with a gun.
You would do it one-on-one
with only the tools
you were born with.
[LOW GROWLING NEARBY]
Dmitri...
get back.
[LOW GROWLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LOW SNARLING]
[SNARLING STOPS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
-[GUNSHOT]
-[SERGEI GASPS]
-[ROARING]
-Dmitri, move!
Move!
[SERGEI CRIES OUT]
Run!
-[GUNSHOT]
-[ROARS]
SERGEI:
Run! [SCREAMING]
[WHIMPERING, SCREAMING]
[SCREAM ECHOING]
[ROARS]
NIKOLAI: [ECHOING]
Sergei!
[LOW GROWLING]
[LAUGHS]
Oh.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Calypso, look.
[DISTANT THUNDER RUMBLING]
CALYPSO'S MUM:
Come on, honey, stand up.
[BIRDS CAWING]
Calypso?
[SIGHS]
Calypso!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[LOW GROWLING NEARBY]
[GROWLING]
[EERIE VOICES ECHOING]
[GROWLS]
[ROARING, SNARLING]
GRANDMOTHER:
In the name of all the spirits
and all the mysteries...
[ECHOING]
mysteries...
CALYPSO: [ECHOING]
Help!
[LOW GROWLING]
GRANDMOTHER: [ECHOING]
Bring the power of the earth.
[ECHOING]
...the power of the earth.
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
Wait.
[RINGING TONE]
-[BIRD SCREECHING]
-GRANDMOTHER: Bring the power
[ECHOING]
of the sky.
[WIND WHISTLING]
[FLATLINE TONE BEEPING]
Everybody's clear.
Shocking now.
[ELECTRICAL THUMP]
[FLATLINE TONE CONTINUES]
Okay, team,
we've done all we can.
I'm going to call
time of death, 6:51.
[FLATLINE TONE CONTINUES]
[SNARLING]
-[ROARS]
-[GASPS]
-[MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY]
-[BREATHING SOFTLY]
[INDISTINCT P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT]
DOCTOR: The EMTs found
that card in your pocket.
You are one very lucky boy.
Thank you for saving me.
I wish I could say I did.
But I didn't save you.
I don't understand.
That makes the two of us.
But we're going
to run some tests,
see if we can figure out
what happened.
Sergei.
Dima.
NIKOLAI:
Why did you not shoot?
You must be Sergei's father.
Mr. Kravinoff.
I am here to take him home.
He needs to stay here
and recover.
Clinically, he was dead
for more than three minutes.
He will be leaving with me.
[WOMAN HUMMING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
[DRAWER OPENS]
MOTHER: [VOICE-OVER]
Sergei...
NIKOLAI: [CALLING]
Sergei!
Come down here!
[IMPERSONATING NIKOLAI]
Father is the only animal
that is dreaded.
[LAUGHS] You're getting
too good at that.
You'll be all right.
You almost got
your brother killed.
You almost got yourself killed,
because you were afraid.
Fear will eat you.
It makes you weak.
Are you weak like your mother?
Crazy?
Or are you like me?
Because if you show weakness
to enemies,
it gives them an opening.
You are old enough
to understand.
You know my business. Yes?
One day, you will be in charge.
Dmitri, go.
Dmitri will go back to school
in New York,
and you will stay here.
With me.
I think America is
making you soft.
-It is for your own good.
-[CLOCK CHIMING]
Each of us have a path to walk.
Embrace who you really are,
and you will have the strength
to walk it.
Come.
Come here.
I got you something.
You never have to be
afraid again.
He should've killed you!
What is going on with you?
[GASPING BREATHS]
Sergei! Get back here!
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Are you okay?
-[BIRD CHIRPING]
-[TAPPING ON WINDOW]
[CHIRPING]
[WINGS FLUTTERING,
BIRD SCREECHING]
[GASPING]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
Don't leave me with him.
I'm going.
-I have to.
-Why?
I can't explain it.
Something's happened to me.
What are you talking about?
Do you remember the place
we used to camp?
Where all you could hear
were the crickets and the owls?
And Mom used to sing to us
around the fire?
That land is all
I have left of her.
How does that make it okay?
Picture me there.
[SCOFFS]
I'm sorry, Dima.
I am.
Just go if you're gonna go.
Go.
I won't be gone forever.
Where you headed?
Trying to get out of England.
To Russia.
On this?
You know there's planes
and trains for that, don't you?
You on the run?
Yes.
I am.
Come on, then. Come on.
[WIND WHISTLING]
-[SOFT RINGING IN EARS]
-[DISTANT BELLOWING]
[GALLOPING HOOFBEATS
IN DISTANCE]
[GALLOPING HOOFBEATS CONTINUE]
[BELLOWING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[THUNDERING HOOFBEATS]
[BELLOWING]
[BELLOWING CONTINUES]
[SNORTING, BELLOWS]
[BELLOWING]
[WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY]
[WOMAN SINGING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
[SINGING GROWS LOUDER]
[SINGING CONTINUES
WITH LYRICS IN RUSSIAN]
[DISTANT THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SINGING CONTINUES]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
NIKOLAI: [VOICE-OVER]
She was weak.
Sick in her mind.
SERGEI: [VOICE-OVER] She died
because you sent her away.
Sergei!
-[ROARING]
-Run!
-[THUNDER CRASHING]
-[ECHOING] Sergei!
[BRANCH CRACKING]
[VOICE-OVER]
Fear will eat you.
It makes you weak.
Each of us has a path to walk.
They are prey.
[GALLOPING HOOFBEATS]
We are predators.
[METALLIC RINGING]
[BLOWS]
[BELLOWS]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING, LAUGHS SOFTLY]
[WATER RUNNING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[DISTANT GUNSHOT ECHOING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
[DISTANT GUNSHOT ECHOING]
[GASPS]
[INSECTS BUZZING]
[CLICKING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[EERIE VOICES ECHOING]
[SERGEI YELLS]
-[GRUNTING]
-[BLOWS LANDING, CRUNCHING]
[WOMAN SINGING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SINGING FADES]
PILOT: [OVER RADIO]
Welcome home.
We stayed under the radar
as usual.
Call me when you need me again.
[DOORS WHIRRING OPEN]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[PHONE BEEPING]
NIKOLAI: [RECORDING]
Sergei, it is your father.
Come home. I miss you.
I am sorry for everything
that has happened.
-[LAUGHTER OVER PHONE]
-[SCOFFS]
DMITRI: Just kidding.
It's your brother.
I texted you.
Where have you been?
[SPLASHING]
-[GRUNTING]
-[CHUCKLES] Oh.
Are you still hiding out
in the woods, huh?
Am I gonna see you
-for my birthday?
-Hmm.
Call me back.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[GROANS]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
-[DISTANT GUNSHOT ECHOING]
-[MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER
IN RUSSIAN]
[ENGINE IDLING]
-Move.
-[TRUCK ENGINE REVVING]
Because we can.
Because you can?
Out of the way.
There's six of us
and only one of you.
There are six of you now.
I ain't got time for this.
I've got deadlines.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[GEARS SHIFTING,
ENGINE ACCELERATING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING VICIOUSLY]
[GRUNTING]
[SPITS]
Go, go!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BIRDS CAWING]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
Mr. Tagland.
I apologize.
This guy,
he came out of nowhere.
A crazy local or...
I don't know.
But I took care of it.
He won't be
bothering us anymore.
In a moment, you won't be
bothered by much of anything.
How did you...?
Where's Mr. Tagland?
Oh, you're standing in him.
Found this.
Interesting read.
You're a poacher.
Mr. Tagland, he hires poachers,
but these names...
drugs, weapons, trafficking.
No, no, I, um...
What's your name?
Andre.
Andre who?
The-the men in that book,
they're the ones you want.
They're the ones in charge.
I-I-I can help you find them.
I don't need your help.
But I will be adding
these names to my list.
Andre who?
Lavigne.
Pretty low on
the pecking order, Andre.
[SIGHS]
Oh. Found you.
[CRIES OUT]
[DISTANT THUNDER RUMBLING]
NEWSWOMAN: [OVER SPEAKER]
And now, today's headlines.
Crusading London prosecutor
Samantha Hodges
was gunned down last week
in broad daylight
following a string
of vicious attacks
targeting law enforcement
and the judiciary.
Memorial services
will be held later today.
[CLOSES LAPTOP]
[SNIFFLES]
CALYPSO: I met Samantha
when I first moved to London.
She was a mentor,
a dear friend,
and one of the fiercest
fighters for justice
this city has ever known.
We all know who did this.
Samantha dared to stand
in Semyon Chorney's way
and hold him accountable.
And for that act of courage,
she lost her life.
This system's broken.
[LOW CHATTER]
-I'm sorry about your friend.
-Shit.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Well, you did.
Sorry for your loss.
Did you know her well?
Actually, I didn't
know her at all.
Well, then, thank you
for the condolences.
Calypso.
I think this belongs to you.
You're...
You're the boy.
But no, you were...
-You were re--
-I was.
For three minutes.
Would have been
a whole lot longer
if you hadn't been there.
Those were
my grandmother's cards.
I actually still carry
the deck with me.
So, why'd you give it to me?
Guess I thought you needed it.
This all you had to go on?
How'd you find me?
Hunting people down
is sort of my thing.
Hunting?
You know who did this?
Yeah, I do.
They gonna get him?
Probably not.
What would you say
if I told you...
...I already did?
A tiger's tooth?
I use whatever tools
are available.
Why would you do that?
Wasn't he responsible
for killing your friend?
Look, I've been trying to
find you for a very long time.
This is my way of saying
thank you for saving my life.
I didn't ask you
to murder anyone.
I'm a lawyer.
But that bastard got
what he deserved.
I know who your father is.
You're like him?
A gangster?
No.
I grew up watching my father
put evil into the world.
The old man had it
all figured out.
I was supposed to follow
in his footsteps
and take over
the family business.
Something happened to me
that day you found me.
So, I got as far away
from my father as I could.
And now I do what I can
to get rid of people like him.
So, you're The Hunter?
That's just what they call me
in the press.
I prefer Kraven.
Kraven?
Hmm. With a "K."
Hmm.
But the only people who have
heard that name are dead now.
Then I guess I'll just
have to watch my back.
[SERGEI LAUGHING]
CALYPSO:
So, do you live here?
[STAMMERS]
I live about as far away
as you can possibly get
from this place.
But my brother does.
We, um...
[SIGHS]
I wasn't always there
for him, so I...
check in when I can.
What about you?
How'd you end up here?
Some days, I'm not so sure.
Um...
My parents were lawyers,
so that's what I did.
I was in the D.A.'s office
in New York for seven years
until I couldn't
take it anymore.
Sometimes, the law can
get in the way of justice.
It can.
Now I'm in London,
at one of the biggest law firms
in Europe.
I know where you work.
You're one of the best
investigative lawyers
in that place.
I also know...
all your clients
aren't exactly angels.
That's true.
So, what are you really getting
done from behind that desk?
I have a list.
A list?
There are other ways to do
what you set out to do,
Calypso.
[PAPER RUSTLING]
Well, you're gonna need
a lawyer, or worse,
if you keep messing around
in this world.
What about a partnership?
From inside that firm,
you can find people I can't.
-And then I could do what...
-Yeah, I get it.
I'll think about it.
Kraven.
And a little friendly advice.
If you keep going after
the names on that list,
people you care about
are gonna get hurt.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
ALEKSEI:
Hey. Raja.
We need to talk about this.
-Yes. We go again?
-[RAJA PANTING]
Go. Go.
[GASPING FOR BREATH]
-Did you hear me?
-[BREATHLESSLY] Raja.
Raja.
Come on, give it here.
Oh, you're going
to make me beg?
You know I don't beg.
You think I'm weak?
-Give me the damn thing.
-[GROWLING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
-Raja!
-[WHINES]
It's okay, Ryazhenka. Yes.
You're my... [SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
Papa loves you.
Papa forgives you.
One more thing.
Semyon Chorney was killed
in his prison cell.
Who got to him?
They're saying
it was The Hunter.
Faster than a cheetah.
Cunning as a fox.
More ferocious than a tiger.
[LAUGHING]
Tell me, do you think
this Hunter actually exists?
Could be a load of bollocks.
But then again,
I hear he's got a list.
Once you're on it,
you never come off.
And there's a good chance
you're on it.
If he is real, he can be found.
I'll do some digging.
Wait.
Chorney's operations
are up for grabs, no?
Set a meet.
His top three guys.
[ENGINES REVVING]
Your boss, Semyon Chorney,
is dead.
I intend to assume control
of his asset transactions.
One of you will be my partner.
Who's it going to be?
[CHUCKLING SOFTLY]
The best pitch wins.
But don't you want to know
why they call me The Rhino?
[SOFT HISSING]
Why do it to yourself?
They have to see
who they're dealing with.
[SKIN CRACKLING]
[CRACKLING CONTINUES]
[RAJA WHINING]
Oh, it's okay, Raja.
It's okay.
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[SKIN CRACKLING]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[CRACKLING SUBSIDES]
[GRUNTING]
You can put your guns away.
If I want you dead,
I only have to raise my...
Don't.
When a rhino sees
his opportunity,
he doesn't hesitate.
He charges in and takes it.
So, I'll ask one more time.
Which one of you
is going to be my partner?
-[GRUNTS]
-[GUNSHOT ECHOES]
Hell of a pitch.
We have a winner.
[ALEKSEI LAUGHING]
[PIANO PLAYING
"SIGN OF THE TIMES"]
[IMPERSONATING HARRY STYLES]
♪ Just stop your crying ♪
♪ It's a sign of the times ♪
♪ Welcome to the final show ♪
♪ Hope you're wearing
your best clothes ♪
[LOW CROWD CHATTER]
♪ You can't bribe the door
on your way to the sky ♪
♪ You look pretty good
down here ♪
♪ But you ain't really good ♪
[SONG ENDS]
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
My son Dmitri.
This next one's for you, Papa.
[PLAYING "THEY CAN'T
TAKE THAT AWAY FROM ME"]
[IMPERSONATING TONY BENNETT]
♪ The way ♪
♪ You wear your hat... ♪
[CHUCKLES]
He does for me.
He knows I like Tony Bennett.
Do you like Tony Bennett?
I don't trust anyone
who doesn't like Tony Bennett.
♪ The memory of all that... ♪
He can do anyone.
He's like chameleon.
♪ They can't take that
away from me... ♪
These assassins, if they can
get to your boss in cage,
I think we all need
to take precautions.
I understand.
Hmm. Come closer.
Chorney, he is gone.
That makes your operations
become vulnerable.
I can offer you security,
distribution,
and most critically,
peace of mind.
Sounds good. I'm on board.
Just like that?
You don't want
to think about it?
-Order has to be restored.
-[NIKOLAI CHUCKLES]
The sooner, the better.
[NIKOLAI CHUCKLES]
You have already done deal,
didn't you?
Who with?
The Rhino sends his regards.
-[GRUNTING]
-[PATRONS SCREAMING]
[WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING]
[PANICKED SHOUTING, SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING FADES]
[GLASS CLATTERS UNDER FEET]
[DMITRI WHIMPERING]
Get up.
[BREATHING RAGGEDLY]
You're hit.
Are you all right, Papa?
[BOTTLE CLATTERS ON FLOOR]
Look at what they have done
to my club.
I get attacked
on my own ground...
...and who do I have
to defend me?
My son, the piano player.
Go on! Hit me!
Fight me!
I need fighters, not coward.
You won't even defend yourself.
[CLATTERING]
The Kravinoff hit failed.
All of our guys are dead.
[RESTRAINED SCREAMING]
Nikolai is a tough old bear.
He won't go quietly, you know.
I found this
slipped under my door.
ALEKSEI: Nikolai Kravinoff's
son, Sergei, is The Hunter?
But what is this, uh, Kraven?
Apparently, that's what
he calls himself.
This can't be real.
-Can it?
-Not sure.
Put The Foreigner on this.
He's a bit of a freak,
but he's been obsessed
with The Hunter for years.
Maybe he can figure out
what the fuck is going on.
Hey.
[ECHOING]
One.
Two.
[ECHOING]
Three.
[GASPS, GRUNTING]
[GUN DROPS ON GROUND]
I'll be seeing you.
[TRAFFIC PASSING]
-[PIGEONS COOING]
-[HORNS HONKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[SHOWER RUNNING]
[SIGHS]
[WATER STOPS]
SERGEI:
Surprise!
-[SCREAMS] Jesus!
-[LAUGHING]
Sergei!
-[YELLS]
-[CHUCKLING]
You scared the shit out of me.
Happy birthday, baby brother.
Mwah.
I love you, man.
[LAUGHING]
What are we gonna do, huh?
Well, you're not wearing that.
-Great, let's stay in.
-What?
It's my birthday.
On your birthday,
we can go to the petting zoo,
or wherever it is
you let loose.
But tonight, this.
What makes you think
I can fit in that?
This is too big on me,
so it would be perfect for you.
-Sorry.
-Thank you.
Pleasure.
Nice perfume, by the way.
Thanks, but I'm not
actually wearing any.
[SNIFFS]
[WHISPERS]
No.
She was gonna find out
soon enough.
DMITRI:
Papa was sitting right here.
It all happened so fast.
You find out what you're
made of in a moment like that.
I'm a coward.
Dima, you're not a coward.
It's natural to feel fear.
That's just
your instinct talking.
Why don't we get
to choose who we are?
Why do I have to be me?
I need to be strong, fearless.
I would run towards
the bullets.
I won't crumble to the ground.
Dima, why would you want
to be anybody but yourself?
So he'd respect me for once.
Papa's a criminal.
So, what good is his respect?
You act like you don't care
what he thinks.
That you're... you're above it.
-That he can't touch you.
-Well, he can't.
He made you hate people.
I don't hate people.
I hate what people do,
but I don't hate people.
I guess, then,
Papa was right about one thing.
Yeah? What's...?
[IMPERSONATING Nikolai]
Men should be the only animal
that is dreaded.
NIKOLAI: I'm glad
I didn't miss the party.
[DMITRI CHUCKLES]
-How could I stay away...
-DMITRI: Papa.
...and miss the chance
and see both my sons?
Dmitri.
-For you.
-Aw.
I don't expect you to give me
a hug, but a handshake?
Hmm.
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
I just came for one toast,
to honor Dmitri on his big day.
Pour.
[GLASSES CLINKING]
Pour for men, not for boys.
Come on, Sergei.
[CLEARS THROAT]
To the Kravinoffs.
Maybe we'll learn someday
to forget the past
and imagine future, together,
as family.
-Na zdorovie.
[GLASSES CLINK]
[DOOR OPENS]
-[DMITRI LAUGHING]
-SERGEI: Okay.
There we go.
[GRUNTS]
You okay?
Sergei.
Huh?
I know why you come every year.
'Cause you feel guilty
for leaving me with him.
I forgive you.
For... everything.
I'm sorry.
[RATTLING]
[RATTLING AND WHIRRING]
[SIGHS, CLEARS THROAT]
[WOMAN SINGING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
MOTHER: [VOICE-OVER, ECHOING]
Sergei! Sergei!
[SINGING, RATTLING AND WHIRRING
CONTINUE]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[WOMAN SINGING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[SIGHS]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[BUTTON CLICKS]
Hold that, will ya?
-[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
-Please? Buddy?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
Uh, penthouse, please.
-I tried to hold it for you.
-No, you didn't.
This?
Oh, it's my travel knife.
Use it for work.
-[KNIFE CLICKS SHUT]
-Ah.
What do you do
for work, exactly?
I hunt.
People.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Dmitri?!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
DMITRI:
Please, please. Let go. Ah.
[GROWLS]
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Stop! Please, please!
Wait, wait, wait.
We-we can figure this out.
ÖMER:
Put him under.
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
ÖMER:
There he is.
Lose him.
SERGEI:
Get the fuck out of the way!
WOMAN:
Watch it.
[GROWLING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GRUNTING]
[HORN BLARING]
[GROWLING]
[YELLING]
-[SERGEI GRUNTS]
-[TIRES SQUEALING]
Fuck!
Go!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
-Faster!
-[SERGEI YELLING]
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Dmitri!
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
It's bulletproof, idiot,
inside and out!
[DOOR HANDLE RATTLING]
[HORNS HONKING]
Get him off!
[GRUNTING]
[HORN HONKING]
[GRUNTING GROWL]
[YELLING]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[BULLETS RICOCHETING]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS FIERCELY]
[YELLS]
-Go! Go!
-[ALARM BEEPING]
[GROWLING]
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
-[SHARP CLANG]
-[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
Dima!
RECEPTIONIST:
Hello, sir.
Is there something
I can help you with?
A towel, maybe?
CALYPSO:
Thank you so much.
[SLOWLY]
Appreciate it.
WOMAN:
Oh.
SECURITY GUARD:
Sir.
I think you left your shoes
in the lobby.
-I'm pretty sure I didn't.
-Why don't we go down
and have a look together?
There ain't enough volts
in the world
-there, my friend.
-Ryan.
Everything's fine.
He's a client.
What the hell, Sergei?
I told you
I'd think about your offer.
You cannot come in here
like this.
This is my place of business.
They got my brother.
Who got your brother?
There were four of them.
Took him from his place.
So, you saw them?
There was this one guy.
Dark hair, brown eyes.
He's got a scar
under his left eye.
Sounded Turkish.
Jesus.
You spoke to them.
Not exactly.
But there was
some screaming involved.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
Let's get into it, then.
I should've been there for him.
I couldn't sleep, so...
I left and went for a walk
and my...
-We're gonna find him.
-[SIGHS]
Okay?
I'm gonna do what I do,
get us a name.
And then you are going to do
what you do.
And we will get him back.
I'm looking for a mercenary
who just ran a kidnapping op
in London.
Moon-shaped scar
under his left eye.
Smokes Turkish cigarettes,
probably a national.
Find him.
NIKOLAI:
Sergei.
-Who are they?
-They would not say.
But you know, don't you?
My list of enemies is long.
Look what they did to him.
How much do they want?
20 million in 48 hours.
[SETS BOX ON DESK]
Pay them.
It is complicated.
No, it's not. It's very simple.
You have the money,
and he's your son.
This is not about money.
This is about power.
If I pay, I am weak.
If I show weakness,
I begin to lose everything
I've spent lifetime building.
A lifetime building what?
You're a drug dealer.
[GROWLING SIGH]
You don't get
to do that anymore.
Dmitri is innocent.
You let him die,
his blood is on your hands.
On my hands?
My hands?
I did not abandon him.
You abandoned him.
You.
He was dead
the moment he was taken.
Whether I pay or not.
No, you do--
You don't know that.
Yes, I know.
Because that is
what I would do.
You're despicable.
Of course I want him back.
I want both my sons back.
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
Some legend you've become.
Wake up.
[DMITRI PANTING]
-[PILLS RATTLING]
-Take these.
-[GROANS]
-Antibiotics.
I can't have you dying
on me, can I?
[IMPERSONATING ÖMER] Can't
have you dying on me, can I?
[BOTTLE CLATTERING]
[LAUGHS SOFTLY]
That's good.
[SNIFFING]
[GRUNTS]
[PILLS RATTLING]
Ömer Ozdemir.
He's holed up in a monastery
in the outskirts of Ankara.
Thank you.
You can thank me
by never calling me again.
We'll see.
THE FOREIGNER:
How'd it go?
She took it.
Of course she took it.
But did she believe you?
Yeah. She trusts me.
Hmm.
Which is why I want double
what your boss promised.
Double?
Why not triple?
What game are you playing?
[THE FOREIGNER LAUGHS SOFTLY]
[ECHOING]
One.
Two.
[ECHOING]
Three.
-[PHONE RINGING]
-[GUNSHOT OVER PHONE]
It's done.
[SPEED DIAL TONES BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
[LINE CLICKS]
Get ready.
The Hunter is on his way.
CALYPSO: [OVER PHONE] Sergei,
the man you're looking for
is Ömer Ozdemir.
I found an old monastery
in his family name in Turkey.
And that is where
you'll find your brother.
Thank you for this.
-[ENGINE IDLING]
-All right, Ellie, let's go.
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
[MEN SPEAKING TURKISH NEARBY]
[HINGES CREAKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MAN SPEAKING TURKISH
OVER RADIO]
-[BLOWS]
-[BODYGUARD GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DISTANT BANGING]
-[BLOWS]
-[CLATTERING]
[BODYGUARDS SPEAKING TURKISH]
[BODYGUARDS CONTINUE
SPEAKING TURKISH]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SPEAKING TURKISH]
[BODYGUARD CONTINUES
SPEAKING TURKISH]
-[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
-[SHARP POP]
[BODYGUARDS EXCLAIMING]
[BODYGUARD SPEAKING TURKISH]
It's him.
[BODYGUARD SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[CRIES OUT]
[BODYGUARD SCREAMING]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
He's there.
[BODYGUARDS CRYING OUT]
Where's Dmitri?!
[YELLING]
[ÖMER GASPING]
Where is he?
Drop me and you'll never
find your brother...
Kraven.
[WHOOSHING]
[ÖMER SCREAMING]
[PAINED GRUNTING]
How do you know my name?!
Who set me up?!
Who took my brother?!
The Rhino.
He's killed us both now.
[RUMBLING]
[GRUNTING]
[POLICEMEN SPEAKING TURKISH
IN OTHER ROOM]
[POLICEMEN CONTINUE
SPEAKING TURKISH]
POLICEMAN:
Hey.
This is crushed rosary peas.
The man who did this
knows his toxins.
[ECHOING]
One.
Two.
[ECHOING]
Three.
What are you doing?
[CHOKING]
-[GASPING]
-Be seeing you.
[BODY THUDS]
[RAJA BARKING]
-[SNAPS FINGERS]
-That's enough, Raja.
Ah, hmm. I'm very sorry
about your finger.
Collateral damage.
-[BARKS]
-Cut him free.
[RAJA PANTING]
We met once,
on your father's hunting trip.
DMITRI:
I, uh, don't remember.
No, you wouldn't.
My hair was different.
You were very young.
Me?
I never forgot.
So, have you spoken
to my father?
Has he agreed to pay?
[LAUGHING]
No.
Nikolai Kravinoff was never
going to hand over $20 million
to get his bastard son back.
You're an accident, Dmitri.
You came into this world
as an accident,
and you came into my possession
as an accident.
So, can I go?
Those men who took you,
they weren't there for you.
They were there
for your brother.
Sergei?
Both of you went in,
but when my guys got up there--
poof-- he'd vanished.
As he always does.
So, I took you.
I got lucky.
Why would you ever want Sergei?
He never hurt anyone.
You really don't know, do you?
Know what?
ALEKSEI:
Wait for the end.
That's the best part.
DMITRI:
Kraven?
Apparently, that's what
he calls himself now.
You think my brother Sergei
is The Hunter?
The Hunter is a story.
A fable to put fear
into criminals.
Clearly, you didn't know
your brother very well.
What do you mean "didn't"?
Kraven had a list.
Once you're on it,
you never come off.
So, I went after him first.
[ROCKS CLATTERING]
Let me record this.
We've got Kraven.
Eh, I don't know about that.
[PAINED GRUNTING]
-[BONE SNAPS]
-[GRUNTS]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[PHONE BEEPS]
-Hello?
-SERGEI: Calypso, it's me.
The whole thing was a trap.
The Rhino, he knows who I am.
-He'll be after you next.
-Sergei, what are you...?
Shit.
There are five guys walking
into my building right now
who do not look like
they belong here.
You need to get
out of there now.
Get to the cargo terminal
at Stansted.
I'll have someone
meet you there.
I call this my feed bag.
It's a mixture of medications
to manage my condition.
What happened to you?
I was underestimated, too.
In and out of hospitals.
They never quite knew
what was wrong.
I knew I would never have
your father's respect...
or anyone else's,
until I was strong.
I tried everything.
-And then...
-[ZIPPER WHIZZING]
...I found someone.
In New York,
a biochemist, a professor,
Miles Warren.
He was developing a procedure
to increase strength, tenfold.
I signed up on the spot.
My skin, it started to harden.
-[SKIN CRACKLING]
-I was indestructible,
like a rhino.
[STRAINING]
But the pain...
...it was too much.
[INHALES]
[SIGHS]
I think there is an animal
in each one of us, Dmitri.
I'm taking over
your father's territory.
I want you to be my partner.
The Kravinoff name
still opens a lot of doors,
and you'll finally get
the consideration you deserve.
You're right.
I have been underestimated.
My whole life.
But if you think
I'm gonna betray my family,
you're wrong.
[GUN RACKS]
Boss, the boys haven't
checked in.
I can't reach 'em.
Kraven is alive.
Hey, Bert!
Alpha team, Bravo team.
He's here.
-[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
-[RAJA BARKING]
[BELL CONTINUES DINGING]
[SNARLING, BARKING]
[WHISTLING JAUNTY TUNE]
[WHOOSHING]
[RAJA PANTING]
Cute.
Will your trick still work
when I remove your eyeballs
from your head?
Relax.
[ENGINE WHIRRING LOUDLY]
I'm sorry I got you
wrapped up in all this.
-Any word on Dmitri?
-Not yet.
Three of my sources
have gone offline
while tracking
The Rhino's plane.
I don't like
the feel of this at all.
CALYPSO:
So, what is this place?
SERGEI: My mother's family
used to own this property.
Well, it's really the only
thing I have left from her.
What is happening right now?
We're being hunted.
By who?
[VICIOUS ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[SNARLING]
[BOTH GROWLING]
[PANTING]
-[GRUNTING]
-[ROARS]
You don't hunt me.
-[HISSING]
-Yeah, get pissed.
What are you gonna do?
Come on, show me.
[BOTH GROWLING]
[SNARLING]
I've seen her around
since she was a cub,
but she's a lot bigger
than I remember.
Oh, you're a goddamn lunatic.
I swear.
Oh, you just
figure that out now?
I know I hired you for the job,
but what is Kraven to you?
Why the obsession?
My mentor was one of
the greatest assassins
who ever lived.
He taught me everything I know.
He was like a brother to me.
Maybe you knew him?
Hmm. Of him.
He was murdered.
One man made it inside
and cut his throat.
Kraven?
So, I traveled the world,
followed him wherever he went.
But Kraven is
nature's perfect predator.
He has no known weaknesses.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
But you found one.
And I know how to exploit it.
Well, get to the part
where I start to give a shit.
These are
Eastern Siberian rosary peas.
A rare species.
I found their residue
on a poison in the monastery.
These peas are only native to
a specific region in Siberia.
That's where we'll find him.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CLICKS]
[SHORT LAUGH]
[WHIRRING]
[DOOR OPENS]
SERGEI:
Whoa, careful with that.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Actually, I'm pretty good
with one of these things.
Archery at summer camp.
Figwort.
Wood avens.
Tribulus.
Mm-hmm.
Rosary peas?
You seem to know your stuff.
They'll kill you.
Or save you.
Nature's funny like that.
What are you trying to do here?
Tell me about this.
It was my grandmother's.
We were on safari
visiting her that day.
I've been trying to figure out
what was in here for years.
My grandmother was
kind of a... mystic.
She had a lot of
crazy stuff around.
My parents didn't like
to talk about it,
but she was
a very powerful woman.
She said it would heal
whoever drank it,
in undreamed-of ways.
I was... I was just a kid.
I didn't know
what it would actually do.
This saved my life.
Did it?
-Trust me. It changed me.
-Exactly.
Look at what you became.
I need to know
what was in here.
And if you can get any more.
No.
She died not long after
that trip,
and I never saw her again.
I heard back
from one of my sources.
The Rhino's on the move.
We should know more very soon.
I knew you'd be good at this.
Sergei, we're gonna
get Dmitri back,
but is all of this
really worth it?
Calypso, I was made to do this.
I'm the greatest hunter
on this planet.
It's undeniable.
There's nobody I can't track
down, nobody I can't beat.
There's nobody can
even touch me, so, no.
Why would I want to stop?
It's called karma.
She catches up to you.
Not me.
I'm faster than she is.
But Dmitri wasn't.
Interesting piece.
It's gonna take more than
a gun to kill Kraven.
I find this formula
that was developed by MI6
to be particularly effective.
May I?
-[RAJA WHINING]
-[THE FOREIGNER CLEARS THROAT]
It first brings on
your darkest nightmares,
then paralysis
of your vital organs,
before a most violent death.
[LAUGHING]
I like your style.
[PHONE RINGING]
Only one person
has this number.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Dima, where are you?
Sergei, I'm sorry.
They made me call you.
SERGEI:
Dmitri.
ALEKSEI:
Afraid not.
But now you know he is alive.
What do you want?
A life without looking
over my shoulder.
You have two choices.
I know you hate your father
as much as I do,
so you and I,
and young Dmitri here,
we work together.
You could be my partners.
Or I kill you and burn...
[PHONE BEEPS]
Okay, then.
Now we go hunt the hunter.
[CHAINS RATTLING]
Spread out.
Bring me his body...
or don't come back.
[WHIRRING]
Raja.
[RAJA GROWLING]
Where is he?
[BARKING]
He's already here.
-[SNARLING]
-[SCREAMING]
MAN:
Oh, shit! Look out!
[SNARLING]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
-[SCREAMS]
-[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[CRIES OUT]
-[TRAPS SNAPPING]
-[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING]
[MEN SCREAMING IN AGONY
IN DISTANCE]
Amateurs.
So embarrassing for us.
Do it.
-[RADIO BEEPS]
-Start the run.
[GRUNTING VICIOUSLY]
-[GRUNTS]
-[CRIES OUT]
Fire in the hole.
You got to be kidding.
[GRUNTS]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BIRDS CAWING]
-[DART THUMPS]
-[CRIES OUT]
Whoa.
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[WHIMPERING]
[YELLING]
[DISTORTED VOICES SINGING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[SERGEI GASPING IN FEAR]
[WHIMPERING]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTS]
THE FOREIGNER: [ECHOING]
The hallucinations
are just the beginning.
Are you seeing
your worst nightmares?
[ECHOING]
One.
Two.
[PANTING]
-[ECHOING] Three.
-[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[ECHOING] As the poison makes
its way to your spinal cord,
you'll begin to lose
all motor functions.
Then asphyxiation.
So, you're the legend.
The myth.
[GRUNTING]
But look at you now.
You're just a man.
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
You give him hell, Kraven.
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THE FOREIGNER BREATHES DEEPLY]
Honestly, I thought
that would be harder.
[STRAINING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
It's done.
But the brother's
still out there.
Go find him.
Let's go.
-[GROANING]
-[ECHOING] One.
[ECHOING]
Two.
-[GRUNTS]
-[GUNSHOT ECHOING]
Three, motherfucker.
Goodbye, Kraven the Hunter.
DMITRI:
Sergei.
BERT: Can't catch a break,
can you, mate?
Legends don't die.
Now get the fuck up, Kraven.
[WHOOSHING]
-Up!
-[GASPING]
[GROANING, COUGHING]
I knew you had more of that.
Well, forgive me
for not trusting a lunatic
with my family's
deepest legacy.
Get up.
[STRAINING]
Okay.
[GROANING]
Well, that must be
some summer camp.
You're not the only one
with secrets.
Don't make me regret this.
BERT:
It's over.
Kraven's dead.
[LAUGHING SOFTLY]
What a day.
[LAUGHING]
Put him in the car.
Who knows?
Maybe Nikolai will pay,
now that he has
only one son left.
[RADIO BEEPS]
Does anyone else see
what I'm seeing here?
[GRUNTS]
[BELLOWING]
[HUFFING]
[ALEKSEI SIGHS]
[HISSING]
[STRAINED GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[SKIN CRACKLING]
[SNORTING]
[BODYGUARDS YELLING]
[BELLOWING]
[SCREAMING]
-[BODYGUARD SCREAMS]
-[BELLOWS]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING FIERCELY]
[DEEP VOICE]
Kraven!
-[ALEKSEI YELLING]
-[GRUNTS]
[ALEKSEI GROWLING]
Gosh, you're really heavy.
[ROARS]
[GROWLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[YELLING]
-[SCREAMING]
-[BELLOWING]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Sergei.
[METALLIC CREAKING]
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
[ALEKSEI YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PAINED GROANING]
[YELLING]
[YELLING, GRUNTS]
[GROWLING]
[YELLING]
[CHOKING]
[STRAINING] My father was
right about one thing.
You are nothing.
[SKIN CRACKLING]
[LOW GROWLING]
[CRIES OUT]
[GROANING]
-[ROARS]
-[GRUNTS]
[BOTH YELLING]
[YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
[BELLOWING FADES]
[STRAINED GRUNTING]
[GURGLING, COUGHING]
The video of me,
how did you get it?
[COUGHING, GAGGING]
Who sent it?
[STRAINING] How is it
that even the great hunter
can't see what was always
right in front of him?
[ALEKSEI COUGHS]
[GUN RACKS]
No.
He deserves to die.
And he will.
But, Dmitri, that's not you.
[STRAINED GURGLING]
I wish...
I wish I never met
you Kravinoffs.
[GASPING BREATH]
[EXHALES]
[WIND HOWLING]
[RUSTLING, TWIG SNAPPING]
[SNIFFS]
[ZIPPER WHIZZING]
Sergei.
How did you find me?
I'm a hunter.
It's what we do.
You sent the video
and told The Rhino who I was.
Did you really think
father would not recognize
actions of his own son?
An assassin who uses
all the methods
of animals of the jungle?
You, of all people,
should recognize and appreciate
the beauty of the trap I set.
[SCOFFS]
The Rhino was coming for you.
You weren't strong enough to
fight him off by yourself, huh?
Exactly.
But my son,
my real son, Kraven...
[LAUGHS SOFTLY]
...no one is stronger.
And I knew you would not
go after him for me.
So, I sent him after you.
Some trap.
[EXHALES]
I mean, Dmitri could have died,
but that's the price
of doing business, right?
No, no, no, no, no.
Because I know you would not
let anything happen
to our precious Dmitri.
SERGEI:
Hmm.
Our empire is secure.
So, what now?
Papa, do we...
...forget about the past?
Imagine a future together?
As family.
[SIGHS]
Sergei.
Where are you going?
I could have come for you,
years ago,
but I didn't.
After everything you'd done,
all the pain
you put in the world...
...you were my father.
I still am.
Sit.
"Never fear death."
Isn't that what you taught me?
[BRANCHES CRACKING]
[DISTANT BELLOWING]
[BELLOWING CONTINUES]
[SNARLING ROAR]
[NIKOLAI SCREAMING]
[ROARING CONTINUES]
[PIANO PLAYING "CHANGES"
BY BLACK SABBATH]
DMITRI: [IMPERSONATING OZZY
OSBOURNE] ♪ I feel unhappy ♪
♪ I feel so sad ♪
♪ I've lost the best friend ♪
♪ That I ever had ♪
♪ I'm going through changes ♪
-[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
-SERGEI: Happy Birthday, Dima.
It is a happy birthday.
First one in a long time.
And that's thanks
to you, Sergei.
Ah, come on.
-Or Kraven, should I say.
-Nah.
What do I call you now?
Mr. Kraven?
-You know who I am.
-I know you.
That was, um... hell,
what I went through.
But it also freed me.
U-Um, I feel almost born again.
[SHORT LAUGH]
I found a doctor in New York.
A little unorthodox,
I must admit.
Mm-hmm.
But he really helped me.
I mean...
changed me.
How so?
Hang on a sec.
Huh?
-[WHISPERING]
-Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
Since when did you have friends
in the bratva, huh?
Well, I have business
-with lots of people.
-Business?
I thought you said you were
gonna sell Papa's assets
and get out of the business.
-I changed my mind.
-Dima, I didn't pull your ass
out of the fire so you can
become a man like our father.
Are you serious?
You put my ass in that fire.
You're a man
just like our father.
No, I'm nothing like him.
I have a code.
-And you're different than him?
-I'm better than him.
You're... [CHUCKLES]
You're not better than him.
You're worse.
How did Papa die again?
[SERGEI BREATHES DEEPLY]
A hunting accident, was it?
Don't lie to me.
You think you have
some kind of honor, huh?
Some kind of code?
Bullshit.
You're just another man
hunting for a trophy.
SERGEI:
Hey.
Dmitri.
[SCOFFS]
[SERGEI'S VOICE] You should
see the look on your face.
Hey.
Dmitri.
DMITRI: [NORMAL VOICE]
You know me.
I've always been a chameleon.
It's the one thing
I was ever good at.
Who is this doctor?
What did he do to you?
You want me to be weak,
so that you can be strong.
But I'm strong now.
I can be whoever I want to be.
The Rhino is gone. Dad is gone.
It's all just there,
for the taking.
I'm gonna take it.
You know I can't
let you do that.
Go home, Kraven.
Dad left you something.
[DISTANT SIREN WAILING]
[VOICES SINGING
TRADITIONAL MUSIC FAINTLY]
NIKOLAI: [VOICE-OVER]
"Sergei,
"each of us has path to walk.
"Embrace who you really are,
"and you will have the strength
to walk it.
"You are more than my child.
"You are me.
"And I am you.
"We are hunters.
The greatest
the world has ever known."
[VOICES CONTINUE SINGING
TRADITIONAL MUSIC]
[SINGING ENDS]
[MUSIC ENDS]